{
    "id": "9ce6e97a5020462ab8ba181dc68a1f7f",
    "title": "Too, Too Much Or Too Many",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is …………….. old to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "too many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "204ee4f4718e4ab98943275f3b4d1653"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ………………. cold to go out now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "too many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "087bf379c1114859978747dc9453c65a"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was ……………….. snow to go walking. (",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too many",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8d8d2978dfb74e7ab53bd2795c9822da"
        },
        {
            "question": "You put ………………… salt in the soup.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too many",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e03d4825559d4b7aa91abeff82bcc282"
        },
        {
            "question": "I put down the box because it was ………………. heavy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "too many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7030bc2f96b84255bd7f6e2a547d02c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He does not like women who are …………….. tall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "too many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b5ff1adc5a474aba94a7e2e5743b34ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "I cannot solve this problem – it’s ………………… difficult.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "too many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8bf8fd4dca8a4fb5be43c2bfb2bf34e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have got ………………… work to do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "too many"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "750beb0c1a0943cdb591de193abc9457"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have eaten ..................... rice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "too many"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc4ffd267b674afa96ff3220437b6842"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ask ...................... questions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too many",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "08ca4ee167d344a4bedabed7cda88a41"
        }
    ]
}